Our main research interest is in understanding pathogenesis of cancer using zebrafish and mammalian experimental systems.  Our current research focuses on dissecting cellular and molecular mechanisms underlying pediatric embryonal rhabdomyosarcoma, in particular the key events regulating tumor differentiation, relapse and metastasis. My laboratory utilizes chemical genetic, genomic and genome engineering approaches to identify key driver events of embryonal rhabdomyosarcoma.